Woman's Building
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Grants, 1974-1992, Series 6:; (Box 25-30; 5.3 linear feet)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development Community Block Grant, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Documentation for National Endowment for the Arts Grants, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Ducommun and Gross Foundation, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - El Paso Natural Gas, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - The Film Fund, Video Project Application, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - The Film Fund, "Equal Time in Equal Space" Video Project Application, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - First Interstate Bank of California Foundation, Grant Application, 1984, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Flintridge Foundation, 1987-1990 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - The Fluor Foundation, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - The Footlighters, Inc., 1981 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Foundation for Community Services Cable Television Application, "Women's Achievements," 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), General Guidelines, circa 1979 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Cash Reports, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Continuation Proposal, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Expenses, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Description, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Grant Proposal Drafts, 1979, (2 folders) (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Grant Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Grant Reports, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Initial Proposal, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Memos from FIPSE Office, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Feminist Education Graphics Project" - Reworked Proposal, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), "Image: Intercommunity Multicultural Action through Graphics Education" Grant Proposal, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), Mina Shaughnessy Scholarship Program Application, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), Project Proposal to Los Angeles 200 Committee, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), Writers Grant, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Gannett Outdoor Company, Application for Support of "Textiles as Text: Arts of the Hmong Women from Laos," 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - General Project Development, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - The Getty Grant Program, Application for Publication of The Way We Look, the Way We See: Proceedings from Art Criticism Conference, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Grant Opportunities, 1979, 1988-1980 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Grant Search, 1985, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Grant Updates, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Grants for "Conference on Women's Culture in American Society," 1981 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - GTE Application, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - IBM Corporation, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Inventory of Grant Proposals, 1978-1981 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - J. B. and Emily Van Nuys Charities, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - J. Paul Getty Trust Fund Application, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - J. Paul Getty Trust Fund Application and Contract Agreement, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - J. Paul Getty Trust Fund, A Division of the California Community Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - JVC, Inc. Application, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Kaufman and Broad, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Knapp Communication Corporations, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Lannan Foundation, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Los Angeles Women's Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Los Angeles Women's Foundation, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Los Angeles Women's Foundation Grant, Women's Video Access Project, 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - McDonnel Douglas West Application, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Grants, 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Mitchell Wolfson Family Foundation Application, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Ms. Foundation, Video Grant Application, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Advancement Grant Application, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Advancement Grant Application, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Artist-in-Residence Grant (Jody Pinto), 1980 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Artist-in-Residence Grant (Harmony Hammond), 1980 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Artist-in-Residence Grant (Helen Harrison), 1981 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Artists' Spaces Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, "Aspara: The Role of the Feminine in Cambodian Arts," 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Assistance to Small Presses Grant, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Billboard Project, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Billboard Project, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Challenge Grant, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Community Cultural Center Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Crafts Exhibition Aid, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Applications, Denied, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, "The Dinner Party," 1979 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Design Arts Grant, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Design Arts Grant for Design Feasibility for the Women's Building, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Expanding Public Participation Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, "Feminist Art in Southern California" Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Helen Harrison Grant, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Media Arts Centers, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Media Arts Residency (Linda Montano), 1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Museum Program, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Museum Program (Slide Library), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, New Moves Program, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, New Moves Program, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, New Moves Program, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, New Moves Program, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, New Moves Program, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, New Moves Program, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, "Public Announcements/Private Conversations," 1981 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, "Public Announcements/Private Conversations," 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Research Grant, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers - "The Extraordinary in Everyday Life: Magical Realism in the Work of Women Writers," 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers - "Mosaic Voices," 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Residencies for Writers - "Three Generations of Black Writers," 1988, (2 folders) (Box 29, Folder 28-29)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Targeted Technical Assistance Project, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, "Textiles as Texts: Art of Hmong Women from Laos," 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, "Those Who Teach," 1985 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Video Production Grant for "Video Quilt: Portraits of Women in Los Angeles," 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Artists Forums Grant, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grant, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grant (Slide Library), 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Organization Grants, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Visual Arts Residencies, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, "Women Bookmakers Forum," 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Women's Caucus for Art Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Women Writers Series, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Application, Women's Video Center Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Designers Panel, Sheila de Bretteville, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Inter-Arts Program Application, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Inter-Arts Program Application, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Inter-Arts Program and Rockefeller Foundation Application, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Work Experience Internship Program, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, "Human Perspectives: Female Artists of the 19th and 20th Centuries," 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Grant Application, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - National/State/County Partnerships, 1985-1988 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - National/State/County Partnerships, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - O'Melveny and Myers, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Orientation Packets for CETA Participants, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Pacific Telesis Foundation, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Pioneer Fund, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Poets and Writers, Inc., Application, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Procedures for Submitting Grants, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Recruiting, Advancement of Instruction and Scholarships for Education of the Graphic Arts (RAISE), Inc., 1986 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Security Pacific Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Skaggs Foundation, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Smithsonian's Experimental Gallery, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Sony Corporation, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Southern California Gas Company, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Support Letters, 1983-1986 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Visit to National Endowment for the Arts in Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Western Airlines Grant Proposal, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Wittner Bynner Application, 1988, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Women's Educational Equity Act Grant Program, Application, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Wonder Woman Foundation Awards, Nomination for Sheila de Bretteville, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Printed Material (Not Woman's Building), 1970-1983, Series 7:; (Box 30-31; 1.3 linear feet)
  This series contains printed materials not produced or related specifically to the Woman's Building, including feminist and art journals, books, exhibition catalogs, and gallery programs.
  - Books - Alix Dobkin's Adventure in Women's Music, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Books - Amazon Baby: Songs for Women, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Books - At Home, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Books - Broadview: An Anthropology of County and City Women Writers, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Books - A Documentary Herstory of Women Artists in Revolution, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Books - The Love Story of Mary Vincent and Laurence E. Cummings, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Books - Mama: Women Artists Together, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Books - Pearls: Writing by South Australian Women, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Books - Women at Work: A Week of Women's Performance, June 1980 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Books - Women's Art Movement, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Books - The Women's Show, Adelaide, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Books - Women's Songbook, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Catalogs, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Catalogs, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Catalogs, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Catalogs, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Catalogs, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Catalogs, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Catalogs, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - The Feminist Art Journal, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Feminist for Women East and West, February 1978 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - motive: on the liberation of women, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - New Directions for Women, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Paid My Dues - A Quarterly Journal of Women in Music, 1979, October-December (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Sisters United, Autumn 1982 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Spare Rib, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Spare Rib, 1980, March-May (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Spare Rib, 1980, June-July (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Spokeswomen, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - WWAC News (Washington Women's Art Center), 1978, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Women, A Berkshire Feminist News Journal, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Women Artists News, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Womanart, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 20)